question_data = [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Vietnamese national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "One of Donald Trumps 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
    ]